Inventory of the Frederick Hutchinson Porter papers, 1880-1975
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
- Photographs:
  - F.H. Porter, Sr., undated (Box 5)
  - Group photograph - from Las Vegas - includes Bunk Porter, undated (Box 5)
  - F.H. Porter, Sr., undated (Box 5)
  - Group Photograph - includes Bunk Porter, undated (Box 5)
  - A.I.A. Convention - Arizona - Mr. and Mrs. Fred H. Porter, Sr. and F.H. Porter Jr., undated (Box 5)
  - Unidentified young boy and girl, undated (Box 5)
  - European trip - arrival in Stockholm - F.H. Porter, Sr., undated (Box 5)
  - The Bunkhouse - Porter residence, undated (Box 5)
  - European trip - F.H. Porter, Sr., undated (Box 5)
  - F.H. Porter, Sr., 1944 (Box 5)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Fred H. Porter, Jr., undated (Box 5)
  - Photograph of sculpture "Mail Walker" in Evanston, Ill. P.O. Robert Russin, undated (Box 5)
  - First Presbyterian Church - Cheyenne, Wyoming, undated (Box 5)
  - Back view of bell tower at Presbyterian Church Center - Washington, D.C. - and looking over the roof of Parsonage Building, April 23, 1974 (Box 5)
  - Banquet - Institute of Architects, undated (Box 5)
  - Board of Directors - American Institute of Architects, January 28, 1960 (Box 5)
  - Breaking of ground ceremony - National Guard Armory - F.H. Porter, July 26, 1967 (Box 5)
  - Building at Warren Airforce Base, undated (Box 5)
  - Cheyenne Frontier Days Committee - F.H. Porter, Sr., undated (Box 5)
  - College of Education Building, University of Wyoming, Laramie, undated (Box 5)
  - Dr. A. Bunten residence - Cheyenne, Wyoming, undated (Box 5)
  - Carbon County Courthouse - Rawlings, Wyoming, undated (Box 5)
  - F.H. Porter, Sr., 1965 (Box 5)
  - F.H. Porter, Sr. friend and one of Porter's paintings, undated (Box 5)
  - F.H. Porter, Sr. friend and painting, undated (Box 5)
  - F.H. Porter, Sr.'s office, undated (Box 5)
  - F.H. Porter, Sr. and paintings, undated (Box 5)
  - Mrs. F.H. Porter, Sr., undated (Box 5)
  - F.H. Porter, Sr., undated (Box 5)
  - Federal building US post office and court house - Cheyenne, Wyoming, undated (Box 5)
  - G.D. Humphrey, undated (Box 5)
  - Geo E. Brimmer House, undated (Box 5)
  - Masonic temple - Cheyenne, Wyoming, undated (Box 5)
  - The 2nd Nagel House - Cheyenne, Wyoming, undated (Box 5)
  - Rev. Pattison - First Presbyterian Church, March 18, 1949 (Box 5)
  - Photograph of sculpture "Steel Workers of Conshohocken, PA" in Conshohocken P.O. Robert Russin, undated (Box 5)
  - Walter Bradley - partner of F.H. Porter, Sr. Architects, undated (Box 5)
  - When F.H. Porter, Sr. received Fellowship Institute of Architects, undated (Box 5)
  - Window in First Presbyterian Church, undated (Box 5)
  - Red Cross volunteers, Mrs. F.H. Porter, Sr., undated (Box 5)
  - The Bunkhouse - Cheyenne, Wyoming - residence of Frederic H. Porter, 1921 (Box 5)
  - State Building (museum) - Cheyenne, Wyoming, undated (Box 5)
  - Tyrrell residence, undated (Box 5)
  - Ellis Hathorne Porter, Jr., undated (Box 5)
  - European trip - F.H. Porter, Sr., undated (Box 5)
  - Richardson family home - razed, September 1968 (Box 1)
  - Cheyenne Frontier Days Committee - F.H. Porter, Sr., undated (Box 1)
  - Photograph of sketch of stained glass window 1st Presbyterian Church - Cheyenne - Bunk Porter, November 1968 (Box 1)
  - Carbon County Court House, undated (Box 1)
  - Photograph of sculptures in front of P.O. - Denver, 1936 (Box 1)
  - Convent - Cheyenne, Wyoming, undated (Box 7)
  - Display - federal buildings of tomorrow, undated (Box 7)
  - Elks Home - Cheyenne, Wyoming, undated (Box 7)
  - I.C. Whipple House - Cheyenne, Wyoming, undated (Box 7)
  - L.C. Hinkle House - later Brimmer home, undated (Box 7)
  - Photograph of sketch of residence of E.W. Whitcomb - Cheyenne, undated (Box 7)
  - Photograph of sketch of residence of H.B. Kelly - Cheyenne, Wyoming, undated (Box 7)
  - Photograph of sketch of 1st Nagel house - Cheyenne, Wyoming, undated (Box 7)
  - Sanctuary of Presbyterian Church - Cheyenne, Wyoming, undated (Box 7)
  - Union Pacific Depot, undated (Box 7)
  - Hi Kelly house, undated (Box 7)
  - Cheyenne Club - Cheyenne, Wyoming, undated (Box 7)
  - Views of P.O. building - Cheyenne, Wyoming, undated (Box 7)
- Programs:
  - "Cheyenne Little Theatre Players (Silver Anniversary)", September 28, 1955 (Box 3)
  - "Cheyenne National Bank is pleased to present an Exhibit of Paintings by Frederic Hutchinson Porter", November-December 1971 (Box 3)
  - "Commencement Exercises of the Cheyenne Senior High School, Sixteenth Annual program", June 9, 1938 (Box 3)
  - "Dedication Ceremony - Federal Building United States Post Office and Court House", June 14, 1965 (Box 3)
  - "Dedication of William Robertson Coe Library and School of American Studies Building, University of Wyoming", October 9, 1958 (Box 3)
  - The Department of Drama of the College of Fine Arts of Drake University presents "Shadow and Substance" by Paul Vincent Carroll - Drake Auditorium, April 1940 (Box 3)
  - "First Presbyterian Church, Our 100th Year", May 25, 1969 (Box 3)
  - "First Presbyterian Church, A Century of Service", June 8, 1969 (Box 3)
  - "First Presbyterian Church, Centennial Banquet", June 13, 1969 (Box 3)
  - "First Presbyterian Church", August 10, 1969 (Box 3)
  - Little Theatre, Cheyenne, Wyoming, season, 1975-1976 (Box 3)
  - Little Theatre (play) A Christmas Carol, 1976 (Box 3)
  - "Official Program of the 71st Annual Cheyenne Frontier Days", 1967 (Box 3)
  - "University of Wyoming Presents Wyoming Cowboys vs. Colorado State Bears", February 1, 1952 (Box 3)
- Scrapbooks:
  - A brochure of the work of Porter and Porter, Architectures - Cheyenne, Wyoming, undated (Box 7-8)
  - Newspaper clippings, undated (Box 7-8)
  - F.H. Porter, Sr., undated (Box 7-8)
  - F.H. Porter, Sr. and architecture in Wyoming, undated (Box 7-8)
  - Architectural projects in Cheyenne and Frontier Days, undated (Box 7-8)
  - F.H. Porter's early days in architecture, undated (Box 7-8)
- Miscellaneous:
  - Announcements of change of address for Porter and Bradley, architectures, June 25, 1947 (Box 3)
  - Blank form - Porter's Market - Emporium and Delicacies - Salem, Mass., undated (Box 3)
  - Calling card - Frederick Hutchinson Porter, architect, undated (Box 3)
  - Christmas greeting card, with photo by Bunk Porter, undated (Box 3)
  - Greeting card (wedding anniversary) from Grace and Fred, October 28, 1914 (Box 3)
  - Menu - The Treagle Wyoming State Tribune Eagle - football special, October 7, 1950 (Box 3)
  - National Register of Historic Places - inventory - nomination form - Union Pacific Depot - Cheyenne, Wyoming, undated (Box 3)
  - National Register of Historic Places - inventory - nomination form - Atlas Theatre, Atlas Building - Cheyenne, Wyoming, undated (Box 3)
  - National Register of Historic Places - inventory - nomination form - Wyoming State Capitol Building and grounds - Cheyenne, Wyoming, undated (Box 3)
  - Picture postcards from Jackson Hole area, undated (Box 3)
  - Postcards, undated (Box 3)
  - Release form for oral history tapes - Wyoming State Art Gallery, February 14, 1975 (Box 3)
  - Report card of Addie Burns - Sparta Public School - high school dept., 1879-1880 (Box 3)
  - Sketch of apartment house for Mr. M.A. Chapman - Cheyenne, Wyoming, undated (Box 3)
  - Thank you card to Pops Bunk and Mama Grace from Rick and Elsie, undated (Box 3)
  - Wedding announcements, undated (Box 3)